<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regina Collins&#39; Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Regina Collins&#39; Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>/posts/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/resume/</guid>
      <description>Click here to view a copy of my Curriculum Vitae. As you will see, I have accumulated a unique set of skills and experiences throughout my studies and my career. Some highlights of my CV include:  I have taught traditional (face to face) and distance/online Information Systems courses at both the undergraduate and graduate level. I have worked as a Research Assistant on a number of projects including Entrepreneurship education, advancing women in STEM, and Open Knowledge Exchange in academic research and publishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/posts/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/publications/</guid>
      <description>My technical writing experience was an excellent preparation for a career as a researcher. In my writing, I focus on presenting information in a clear and concise manner and supporting my results and conclusions with well established theoretical underpinnings.  Share and Share Alike: Integrating Internet Resource Sharing Into Learning - This paper is being presented at the 2015 Americas Conference on Information Systems (AMCIS) as a completed research paper. The research reported in this paper pulls from my doctoral dissertation and a complementary study conducted with other NJIT doctoral candidates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/posts/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Learning to be a teacher - to facilitate the learning of the students in your class - is a critical skill. To ensure that doctoral students are well prepared for careers as instructors, New Jersey Institute of Technology requires that students teach at least one course during their time as a doctoral candidate. I am fortunate to have gained invaluable teaching experience through various stages of exposure to instruction.  I started as a Teaching Assistant for the graduate-level Systems Analysis and Design course for two semesters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>/posts/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/presentations/</guid>
      <description>In addition to papers, an important way for researchers to communicate their work is through posters and presentations.  The following links provide some highlights of my research posters. Presentations can be viewed on SlideShare.  More Than The Sum of Its Parts: Advancing Women at NJIT Through Collaborative Research Networks - Having been nominated to present my research at the Dana Knox Student Research Showcase, I designed this poster to highlight research we were doing to understand the position of women faculty in their departmental social networks, seeking to understand if isolation or other factors caused women faculty to be underrepresented in the university.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Writing</title>
      <link>/posts/technical-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/technical-writing/</guid>
      <description>To better illustrate my technical communication skills, I have included some examples of my work from my Master of Professional and Technical Communication.  CorpCommCollab brochure - I designed this brochure to serve as a marketing tool for a collaborative wiki created by all the students in the Corporate Communication seminar. The brochure is designed to be visually appealing and to provide sufficient information to create interest in our collaborative wiki.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/404/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/404/</guid>
      <description> Error 404: Page Not Found It seems that the page that you&amp;rsquo;re trying to access doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist. 😟 If you&amp;rsquo;re sure that it exists, chances are it might have been moved to a new link! You may search for it on the home page. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>So, Who Am I? 
This website provides examples of my work in Information Systems research, teaching, and Technical Communication. Below is some background information about me.
I originally graduated from NJIT with a Bachelor of Science degree in Computer Science, but realized that my true passion lay in helping people interact with technology. Therefore, upon graduation, I immediately applied for a position as a technical writer, and I worked in that field for 20 years, focusing particularly on software documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>